tenkofx.com 2016-03-15

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how TenkoFx ('the Company') collects and uses information through its site www.tenkofx.com or any other sites that are operated by the Company.

TenkoFx respects the privacy of any visitor that accesses its site(s). The Company is committed to protecting any existing or prospective client, applicant or visitor related information.

Customer registration

In order to open an account with TenkoFX, a customer completes and submits an application form and provides confirming documents required for identity verification purposes. By completing the application form you are requested to disclose private information in order to enable the Company to evaluate your application and comply with relevant rules and regulations.

Confidentiality

TenkoFX shall not disclose to a third party, any of its clients' confidential information unless required to do so by a regulatory authority of a competent jurisdiction; such disclosure shall occur on a 'need-to-know' basis, unless otherwise instructed by a regulatory authority. Under such circumstances, the Firm shall expressly inform the third party regarding the confidential nature of the information.

Clients accept and consent that TenkoFx may, from time to time, contractually engage companies for statistical purposes in order to improve the Company's marketing; as a result, some or all of the clients' personal data may be disclosed on an anonymous and aggregated basis only.

Agents

We use a card processing company for your deposits and withdrawals to and from your TenkoFX trading account; Our services providers do not retain, share, store or use any personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

Privacy

Tracking systems used on the Company's site(s) may collect data detailing the pages you have accessed, how you discovered this site, the frequency of visits etc; this information is obtained in order to improve the content of the Company's site(s) and may also be used by TenkoFx to contact you, through an appropriate mean, and provide you with any information the Firm believes to be useful.

Choice / Opt-out

If you no longer wish to receive any communication from the Company, you may opt-out of by adjusting respective settings in your individual customer area - TenkoDESK.

You shall be notified accordingly if your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/ service provider, so you can make an informed decision as to whether or not you want to share your information with that party.

Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. TenkoFxo uses cookies on its site(s). The Company does not link the information stored in cookies to any personally identifiable information you may submit.

TenkoFX uses both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie does not expire when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's 'Help' file.

TenkoFX sets a persistent cookie for statistical purposes. Persistent cookies also enable the Company to track and target the location and the interests of users that access the TenkoFX site(s) and to enhance the experience of services offered.

Some of the TenkoFX business partners use cookies on the Company's site(s); TenkoFX has no access or control over these cookies.

Protection of your personal information

The personal information that you provide in connection with registering yourself as a user of the site(s) or of the services is classified as 'Registered Information'. 'Registered Information' is protected in many ways. You can access your 'Registered Information' through a password selected by you. This password is encrypted and known only to you. Your password must not be revealed to anyone. 'Registered Information' is safely stored on secure servers that only authorised personnel have access to via password. The Company encrypts all personal information as it is transferred to TenkoFX and thus makes all necessary effort to prevent unauthorised parties from viewing any such information.

Personal information provided to TenkoFX that is not 'Registered Information' also resides on secure servers and is again accessible only by authorised personnel via password this information cannot be accessible by you, therefore no password shall be provided in order for you to modify this.

Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, you must inform us accordingly; please e-mail us at (support@tenkofx.com) or update your profile via TenkoDESK customer area.

Legal Disclaimer

TenkoFX reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by rules and regulations and when the Firm believes that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served. TenkoFX will not be liable for misuse or loss of personal information resulting from cookies on the Company's site(s) that TenkoFX does not have access to or control over. TenkoFX will not be liable for unlawful or unauthorised use of your personal information due to misuse or misplacement of your passwords, negligent or malicious.

Changes in this Privacy Statement

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

Enquiries

If you have any enquiries regarding the 'Privacy Policy' please e-mail us (support@tenkofx.com) or call us +64 9 306 8923

Date: October 11 2013
